Contact

No: 125 Kulugammana, Kandy 0770621334 (Mobile) shashinisaharawerellagama@g mail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shashinisahara-882947212 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

IDEAL

Mindfulness

Science

Certifications

Certificate of Internship recognizes with appreciation as a Campus Ambassador Intern

Letter of Recommendation for working as a campus ambassador for IMUN

Introduction to Chemistry: Structures and Solutions

Certificate of Appreciation For Successfully Participating as a delegate in IMUN ONLINE CONFERENCE 60.0

Introduction to Chemistry : Reactions and Ratios

Shashini Sahara

Undergraduate BSc. Applied Sciences RUSL Kandy District

Summary

I am a second-year undergraduate student of Rajarata University of Sri Lanka from the faculty of Applied Sciences, Biological department. Currently working in Statistic and Data Analytics Study group as an administrator and a member in CKDu risk prediction research group. Contributing as a member of Association of young biologists at RUSL and as a Gavelier in Gavel Club at RUSL. Volunteering for Zero Plastic in Sri Lanka and applied for the leadership position. An undergraduate teaching assistant in course networking. Worked in the Nutrition for Astronauts project at SEDS| OUSL and selected for the top 10 teams won 8th place. Had an internship as an Official Campus Ambassador with International model united nations for 5 months.

Experience

Statistics and Data Analytics Administrator November 2021 - Present (1 month) Sri Lanka

ZeroPlastic Sri Lanka Student Volunteer November 2021 - Present (1 month) Sri Lanka

Rajarata University of Sri Lanka Student Researcher November 2021 - Present (1 month) Sri Lanka

Gavel Club of Rajarata University of Sri Lanka Member October 2021 - Present (2 months)

Sri Lanka

CourseNetworking Undergraduate Teaching Assistant November 2021 - Present (1 month)

A teaching assistant in general physics course

Association of Young Biologists Crew Member July 2021 - Present (5 months) Sri Lanka

International Model United Nations Association (IMUNA) 7 months

Official Campus Ambassador at IMUN May 2021 - November 2021 (7 months) Kandy, Central, Sri Lanka

Official Campus Embassador May 2021 - May 2021 (1 month) Kandy, Central, Sri Lanka

Official Campus Embassador at International MUN May 2021 - May 2021 (1 month) Kandy District, Central, Sri Lanka

Education

Rajarata University of Sri Lanka
Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Biology/Biological Sciences,
General · (2020 - 2024)

ICBT Campus

Diploma in English and IT, English and IT \cdot (2018 - 2019)

Mahamaya Girls' College Kandy Advanced Levels, Bio Science (2016 - 2019)

St.Anthony's Girls' College, Kandy Ordinary Levels · (2005 - 2015)